Guide to the Stanford University, Board of Trustees, Meeting Records SC1010
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University, Board of Trustees, meeting records
1885-2017
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University. Board of Trustees
SC1010
100.5 Linear Feet
The materials consist of Board of Trustees meeting agendas, minutes, and supporting materials.
Access to Collection
The materials are restricted for 20 years from creation date.
Arrangement note
The materials are arranged in two series: 1. Records created prior to 2010; 2. Records created since 2010.
Administrative History
The Board of Trustees of the Leland Stanford Junior University was established on November 11, 1885, by the Grant Founding and Endowing the Leland Stanford Junior University (the "Founding Grant"). The powers and duties of the Board derive from the Founding Grant, amendments, legislation, and court decrees. In addition, the Board operates under its own bylaws and a series of resolutions on major policy.
Although the Founding Grant named the initial group of trustees, they did not hold meetings until 1898. Jane Stanford, the surviving founder of the university, served as president of the Board from 1898-1903. Regular meetings began in 1903 following Jane Stanford's decision to transfer oversight of the university to the Board.
As custodian of the endowment and all the properties of Stanford University, the Board administers the university's invested funds, sets the annual budget, and determines policies for operation and control of the university. Among the powers given to the trustees by the Founding Grant is the power to appoint a president.
As of 2012, Board membership is set at 35, including the President of the University, who serves as an ex officio member with voting privileges. Trustees serve five-year terms and are eligible for appointment to one additional five-year term.
Standing committees of the Board include Academic Policy, Planning, and Management; Alumni and External Affairs; Audit and Compliance; Development; Finance; Land and Buildings; the Medical Center; and Trusteeship. Special committees include Athletics, Compensation, Investment Responsibility, and Litigation.
Scope and Contents note
The materials consist of Board of Trustees meeting agendas, minutes, and supporting materials.
Stanford University -- History.; Stanford University -- Planning.; Stanford University -- Administration.; Stanford University -- Facilities.; Universities and colleges -- Administration.; Universities and colleges -- Faculty.; Stanford University. Board of Trustees; Stanford University -- Finance.
- Records created prior to 2010, 1885-2009; Series 1
  Scope and Contents
  Records created prior to 2010 are arranged in series by format. Subseries 1 comprises agendas distributed to the Board prior to meetings. Subseries 2 consists of meeting minutes. Subseries 3 contains supporting materials related to Board business, such as correspondence and reports.
  A fourth subseries includes both meeting agendas and supporting materials, which were transferred to the University Archives by the Board of Trustees administrative office in 2003 and 2004. Although some duplicate material was removed during processing, overlap still exists between this group of materials and the materials in Subseries 2 and 3.
  Access to Collection
  The materials are restricted 20 years from date of creation.
  - Agendas, 1906-1908; 1955-2009; Subseries 1; 25 Linear Feet (50 boxes)
    This subseries contains agendas distributed prior to meetings of the Board of Trustees. Researchers should be aware that gaps in coverage may exist.
    Restricted 20 years from date of creation.
    - Programs and Agendas, 1906-1908 (Box 1)
    - January 1955-November 1957 (Box 2)
    - December 1957-Jul 1959 (Box 3)
    - September 1959-September 1960 (Box 4)
    - November 1960-April 1961 (Box 5)
    - May-June 1961 (Box 6)
    - July-November 1961 (Box 7)
    - December 1961-April 1962 (Box 8)
    - May-November 1962 (Box 9)
    - December 1962-April 1963 (Box 10)
    - May-December 1963 (Box 11)
    - January-June 1964 (Box 12)
    - July 1964-May 1965 (Box 13)
    - June 1965-February 1966 (Box 14)
    - March 1966-January 1967 (Box 15)
    - February 1967-February 1968 (Box 16)
    - March 1968-March 1969 (Box 17)
    - April 1969-April 1970 (Box 18)
    - June 1970-September 1971 (Box 19)
    - October 1971-January 1973 (Box 20)
    - February 1973-March 1974 (Box 21)
    - April 1974-May 1975 (Box 22)
    - June 1975-September 1976 (Box 23)
    - October 1976-September 1977 (Box 24)
    - November 1977-June 1978 (Box 25)
    - September 1978-April 1979 (Box 26)
    - May-December 1979 (Box 27)
    - February-June 1980 (Box 28)
    - September 1980-March 1981 (Box 29)
    - May-December 1981 (Box 30)
    - February-June 1982 (Box 31)
    - September-December 1982 (Box 32)
    - February-June 1983 (Box 33)
    - September-December 1983 (Box 34)
    - February-June 1984 (Box 35)
    - September-December 1984 (Box 36)
    - February-June 1985 (Box 37)
    - September-December 1985 (Box 38)
    - February-September 1986 (Box 39)
    - October 1986-December 1987 (Box 40)
    - February 1988-February 1989 (Box 41)
    - April 1989-December 1990 (Box 42)
    - February 1991-February 1993 (Box 43)
    - April 1993-April 1995 (Box 44)
    - June 1995-October 1997 (Box 45)
    - December 1997-June 2000 (Box 46)
    - October 2001-June 2003 (Box 47)
    - December 2003-October 2005 (Box 48)
    - December 2005-December 2007 (Box 49)
    - February 2008-February 2010 (Box 50)
  - Minutes, 1885, 1903-2009; Subseries 2
    Board of Trustees minutes document discussions held and actions taken during Board meetings. This subseries contains both official and unofficial copies of minutes. Official minutes are contained in bound volumes and are signed by the Board secretary. Volume 1 is missing and is presumed to have been destroyed in the 1906 San Francisco earthquake and fire.
    Unofficial minutes lack the Board secretary's signature. Researchers should note that the set of unofficial minutes is incomplete.
    - Official (signed)
      - Volume 2, 1904-05-25 - 1906-08-31 (Box 38)
      - Volume 3, 1906-09-28 - 1908-05-29 (Box 39)
      - Volume 4, 1908-05-29 - 1911-03-31 (Box 40)
      - April 28, 1911 - Dec. 26, 1913 (Volume 5) (Box 41)
      - January 30, 1914 - Dec. 29, 1916 (Volume 6) (Box 42)
      - January 26, 1917 - July 9, 1920 (Volume 7) (Box 43)
      - August 2, 1920 - August 14, 1923 (Volume 8) (Box 44)
      - August 14, 1923 (continued) - July 8, 1926 (Volume 9) (Box 45)
      - August 12, 1926 - Dec. 8, 1927 (Volume 10) (Box 46)
      - January 5, 1928 - August 14, 1929 (Volume 11) (Box 47)
      - August 14, 1929 (continued) – February 13, 1931 (Volume 12) (Box 48)
      - February 13, 1931 (continued) - Oct. 13, 1932 (Volume 13) (Box 49)
      - Volume 14, 1932-10-13-1934-05-10 (Box 50)
      - Volume 15, 1934 Jun 14 - 1935 Nov 21 (Box 51)
      - Volume 16, 1935 Nov 21-Dec 19 (Box 52)
      - Volume 17, 1936; 1 volume(s)
      - Volume 18, 1937; 1 volume(s)
      - Volume 19, 1938; 1 volume(s)
      - Volume 20, 1939; 1 volume(s)
      - Volume 21, 1940; 1 volume(s)
      - Volume 22, 1941; 1 volume(s)
      - Volume 23, 1942; 1 volume(s)
      - Volume 24, 1943; 1 volume(s)
      - Volume 25, 1944; 1 volume(s)
      - Volume 26, 1945; 1 volume(s)
      - Volume 27, 1946; 1 volume(s)
      - Volume 28, 1947; 1 volume(s)
      - Volume 29, 1948; 1 volume(s)
      - Volume 30, 1949; 1 volume(s)
      - Volume 31, 1950; 1 volume(s)
      - Volume 32, 1951; 1 volume(s)
      - Volume 33, 1952; 1 volume(s)
      - Volume 34, 1953; 1 volume(s)
      - Volume 35, 1954; 1 volume(s)
      - Volume 36, 1955; 1 volume(s)
      - Volume 37, 1956; 1 volume(s)
      - Volume 38, 1957; 1 volume(s)
      - Volume 39, 1958; 1 volume(s)
      - Volume 40, 1959; 1 volume(s)
      - Volume 41, 1960; 1 volume(s)
      - Volume 42, 1961; 1 volume(s)
      - Volume 43, 1962; 1 volume(s)
      - Volume 44, 1963; 1 volume(s)
      - Volume 45, 1964; 1 volume(s)
      - Volume 46, 1965; 1 volume(s)
      - Volume 47, 1966; 1 volume(s)
      - Volume 48, 1967; 1 volume(s)
      - Volume 49, 1968; 1 volume(s)
      - Volume 50, 1969; 1 volume(s)
      - Volume 51, 1970; 1 volume(s)
      - Volume 52, 1971; 1 volume(s)
      - Volume 53, 1972; 1 volume(s)
      - Volume 54, 1973; 1 volume(s)
      - Volume 55, 1974; 1 volume(s)
      - Volume 56, 1975; 1 volume(s)
      - Volume 57, 1976; 1 volume(s)
      - Volume 58, 1977; 1 volume(s)
      - Volume 59, 1978; 1 volume(s)
      - 1979, 1 volume(s)
      - 1980, 1 volume(s)
      - 1981, 1 volume(s)
      - 1982, 1 volume(s)
      - 1983, 1 volume(s)
      - 1984, 1 volume(s)
      - 1985, 1 volume(s)
      - 1986, 1 volume(s)
      - 1987, 1 volume(s)
      - 1988, 1 volume(s)
      - 1989, 1 volume(s)
      - 1990, 1 volume(s)
      - 1991, 1 volume(s)
      - 1992, 1 volume(s)
      - 1993, 1 volume(s)
      - 1994, 1 volume(s)
      - 1995, 1 volume(s)
      - 1996, 1 volume(s)
        Conditions Governing Access note
        Restricted until Jan 1, 2017.
      - 1997, 1 volume(s)
        Restricted until Jan 1, 2018.
      - 1998, 1 volume(s)
        Restricted until Jan 1, 2019.
      - 1999, 1 volume(s)
        Restricted until Jan 1, 2020.
      - 2000, 1 volume(s)
        Restricted until Jan 1, 2021.
      - 2001, 1 volume(s)
        Restricted until Jan 1, 2022.
      - 2002, 1 volume(s)
        Restricted until Jan 1, 2023.
      - 2003, 1 volume(s)
        Restricted until Jan 1, 2024.
      - 2004, 1 volume(s)
        Restricted until Jan 1, 2025.
      - 2005, 1 volume(s)
        Restricted until Jan 1, 2026.
      - 2006, 1 volume(s)
        Restricted until Jan 1, 2027.
      - 2007, 1 volume(s)
        Restricted until Jan 1, 2028.
      - 2008, 1 volume(s)
        Restricted until Jan 1, 2029.
      - 2009, 1 volume(s)
        Restricted until Jan 1, 2030.
      - Minutes of the Committee on Investments of the Board of Trustees of Leland Stanford Junior University, 1936-1940 (Box 53)
      - Minutes of the Committee on Investments of the Board of Trustees of Leland Stanford Junior University, 1946-1957 (Box 53)
      - Minutes of the Committee on Investments of the Board of Trustees of Leland Stanford Junior University, 1958-1968 (Box 53)
      - Microfilm (Box 54)
    - Unofficial (unsigned), 18.5 Linear Feet (37 boxes)
      - January 1906 - December 1917 (bound volumes) (Box 1)
      - January 1918 - December 1929 (bound volumes) (Box 2)
      - January 1930 - December 1935 (bound volumes) (Box 3)
      - August 1908 - March 1914 (bound volumes) (Box 4)
      - November 1885, August 1903 - December 1907 (Box 5)
      - January 1908 - September 1912 (Box 6)
      - August 1914 - August 1915 (Box 7)
      - September 1919 - August 1931 (Box 8)
      - September 1931 - 1935 (Box 9)
      - January 1936 - July 1937 (Box 10)
      - October 1944 - July 1946 (Box 11)
      - Steptember 1956 - December 1958 (Box 12)
      - January 1959 - March 1961 (Box 13)
      - July 1961 - December 1962 (Box 14)
      - January - December 1963 (Box 15)
      - January - December 1964 (Box 16)
      - January 1965 - June 1966 (Box 17)
      - July 1966 - December 1967 (Box 18)
      - January 1968 - November 1968 (Box 19)
      - January 1969 - May 1970 (Box 20)
      - June 1970 - October 1971 (Box 21)
      - November 1971 - June 1973 (Box 22)
      - September 1973 - November 1974 (Box 23)
      - December 1974 - April 1976 (Box 24)
      - June 1976 - November 1977 (Box 25)
      - December 1977 - October 1978 (Box 26)
      - November 1978 - December 1979 (Box 27)
      - February - December 1980 (Box 28)
      - February - December 1981 (Box 29)
      - February 1982 - March 1983 (Box 30)
      - May 1983 - December 1984 (Box 31)
      - February - December 1985 (Box 32)
      - February 1986 - September 1987 (Box 33)
      - December 1987 - June 1990 (Box 34)
      - October 1990 - July 1991; June 1993; February 1996 - February 1999 (Box 35)
      - April 1999 - April 2004 (Box 36)
      - June 2004 - December 2009 (Box 37)
    - Computer files
      - 2005 Jun 6-7
      - 2005 Oct 10-11
      - 2005 Dec 12-13
      - 2006 Feb 13-14
      - 2006 Apr 10-11
      - 2006 Jun 14-15
      - 2006 Oct 9-10
      - 2006 Dec 11-12
      - 2007 Feb 12-13
      - 2007 Apr 22-25
      - 2007 Jun 13-14
      - 2007 Oct 8-9
      - 2007 Dec 10-11
      - 2008 Feb 11-12
      - 2008 Apr 7-8
      - 2008 Jun 11-12
      - 2008 Oct 13-14
      - 2008 Dec 8-9
      - 2009 Feb 9-10
      - 2009 Apr 13-14
      - 2009 Jun 10-11
      - 2009 Oct 12-13
      - 2009 Dec 7-8
  - Supporting material, 1905-1976, 1998-2009; Subseries 3; 28 Linear Feet (56 boxes)
    Board of Trustees supporting documents include correspondence, reports, surveys, legal documents, and printed material related to matters discussed at Board meetings. For additional supporting materials, see Subseries 4, which contains agendas and supporting material transferred to the University Archives from the Board administrative office in 2003 and 2004.
    - Redeeming Southern Pacific Bonds (letters and resolution), June-July 1905; By-Laws and rules of order of the Bd of Trustees, July 26, 1905, 1905 May 19 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Jordan to Board: Student athletics grounds placed under control of University, Oct. 24, 1905, 1905 Nov 24 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Copies of documents re work on campus buildings; Includes museum, hay barn, boys gymnasium, bookstore, and geology lab. [copied 2007 at History San Jose], 1905 (Box 1, Folder 2.1)
    - Right of way for power line on Vina property (agreement with blueprint map), Feb. 27, 1906, 1906 Jan 26 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Salary roll, 1906-1907, with letters by Horace Davis, Jan. 7, 1906, and Frank Miller, Jan. 1, 1906, 1906 Feb 23 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Note of loan to Board of Trustees from Charles G. Lathrop, March 2, 1906, 1906 Mar 30 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Report of Stanford U. engineers on earthquake damage at Stanford; List of library's books at SF bindery destroyed in fire with letter by David S. Jordan, May 8, 1906; Fees, letters of Jordan and Crothers re; Letters by Jordan transmitting various reports; Resolution of confidence in Charles G. Lathrop's role in construction of University and related letters; Trustee papers lost in fire (partial listing), with letter by Crothers, 1906 May 11 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Commencement program, Sept. 15, 1906; Letters re sabbatical leave request of Prof. J. C. L. Fish, April - July 1906; Extracts from minutes (1905-1906) re sabbatical leaves, 1906 May 25 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence on fees and copy of decision by Wisconsin Supreme Court (1882) on tuition; Legal document and letter re suit by Lagunitas Water Company; Oakland Water Front Co., correspondence re proxy voting powers for Lathrop; G.H. & S.A. income bonds, correspondence regarding; Angel of Grief, agreement with Hector N. Bernieri re construction, August 1906, and letters re shipment, Oct. - Dec. 1907, 1906 Jun 29 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Lease with Delta Upsilon fraternity, Sept. 1, 1906, and related correspondence of Crothers, J. Pearce Mitchell, and Wilson & Wilson, July 3, 1906 - Apr. 23, 1907; Charles Hodges: bill for work on Univ. Library and related correspondence, June 24 - July 17, 1906, 1906 Jun 29 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Faculty housing on campus: correspondence of Jordan and Crothers, and extracts from University trusts relative to the erection of housing; "Report on Condition of Buildings Constituting Leland Stanford Jr. University, California, and Damages Resulting Thereto from the Effects of the Earthquake of April 18, 1906" (3 copies), 1906 Aug 1 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Museum; correspondence re repairs to sculpture damaged in earthquake, Sept. 1, 1906; Faculty housing on campus: report of committee, Aug. 24, 1906, and correspondence of Crothers and Charles P. Eells, June 1907; Phonograph to be used in teaching French: correspondence of John E. Matzke, Jordan, and Crothers re acquisition of, Aug. - Sept. 1906; Stillman Ranch sale to Karl C. Wells, indenture and related correspondence, Aug. 31 - Oct. 31, 1906, 1906 Aug 31 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Library Committee "unit system" proposal re distribution of funds, Aug. 24, 1906, and responses from Profs. J. Elmore, Max Farrand, A. B. Clark, Fernando Sanford, H. W. Rolfe, Melvin G. Dodge, A. G. Newcomer, and E. P. Cubberley; John T. Doyle library purchase, correspondence, Aug. - Dec. 1906, 1906 Aug 31 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Automobiles on campus: letter from R. L. Wilbur requesting permission in relation to his medical services, Sept. 21, 1906; and letter and map by Mr. Draper suggesting route for auto road, Sept. 21, 1906; Richardson, Mrs. Margaret W., lease and related correpondence, 1906 and 1908; Phi Gamma Delta fraternity, lease and related correspondence, Oct. 1-18, 1906; Jordan, D. S. letter urging publication of facts re Mrs. Jane Stanford's death, Sept. 24, 1906; Election of Alumni to the Board: correspondence of Jordan, Crothers, Lathrop, O. E. Elliott, and Frank Miller, July - Sept. 1906, 1906 Sep 28 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Jewel sales: letters and financial documents, 1906-1910; Correspondence re campus survey to plan housing and roads, Sept. 3, 1906 - Jan.2, 1907; Letters to Vanderlynn Stow on his Trustee position, 1906-1907, 1906 Nov 2 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Medical Department: G. J. Peirce to Stillman on the Medical School project, Aug. 16, 1906; Stillman's report on Medical Department, Oct. 17, 1906; Reports on prospective needs of each department for next 5 years (Greek, Latin, English, German, Romanic Languages, Economics & History, Psychology, Education, Law, Zoology, Geology and Mining, Physics, Chemistry, Physiology and Histology, Entomology and Bionomics, Hygiene, Drawing, Mathematics & Engineering, Botany, Registrar's Office, President's Office), 1906 Nov 30 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Fees and possibility of eliminating first two years: correspondence of Crothers, Jordan, and Horace Davis, July 12 - Aug. 23, 1906; Bay Point and Clayton Railroad: correspondence and legal document re right of way through Government Ranch [Contra Costa County], Jan. 2 - Feb. 13, 1907, 1907 Jan 4 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Retirement: correspondence of Jordan and Crothers, Aug. - Oct. 1906, re age of; pamphlet from Carnegie Foundation "Rules for Granting of Retiring Allowances," Apr. 1906; University publications: letter from Crothers to Horace Davis, Dec. 12, 1906; Ryan, Harris J., letter to Jordan re electrical railway line on campus, Sept. 17, 1906, and related correspondence of Jordan and Crothers, 1906 Sep 28 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Alameda County land, right of way to Western Pacific Railway Co., correspondence of Crothers, several officers of the Western Pacific Railway Co., real estate agent E. Leigh, S. F. Leib, and Lathrop, May - Oct. 1906; and an indenture Sept. 1906, 1906 Sep 28 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Stow, Vanderlynn: correspondence and clipping re position on Board; Athletic facilities: letters from Clark W. Hetherington re Stanford's needs and prospects, Oct. 6, 1906, and other letters of Frank Angell and Jordan; Retirement: report of Advisory Board regarding age and conditions of retirement, Oct. 30, 1906, and letter from Jordan, Oct. 31, 1906; Memorial Church chaplain's report, Oct. 16, 1906; Vina Ranch reports, Oct. 18 - Nov. 5, 1906, 1906 Nov 30 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Hetherington, Clark W.: correspondence of R. H. Jesse (U. of Missouri) and Jordan re offer of position at Stanford to Hetherington, Dec. 1906; Proposed salary roll for 1907-08 with cover letter/report from Jordan, Dec. 10, 1906; Financial management: Organization of the Financial Management of the LSJU, n.d. [report], Report of Organization Committee, 1903-1904, By-Laws and Rules of Order, 1904, and Reports of Trustee Sloss on Financial Management and Actions Thereon, 1905-1907, 1907 Jan 4 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Report by R. E. Swain on proposed copper smelter at Baden (on the Peninsula), Jan. 24, 1907; Sale of University lands: "syndicate lands" in Siskiyou county; Government Ranch and other areas in Contra Costa County, 1907 Jan 25 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Theta Delta Chi: correspondence and lease, Nov. 5, 1906 - May 7, 1907; Chicago and Northwestern Railway: correspondenc re bond, Feb. - Mar. 1907; Report on insurance in force, including Vina, Feb. 25, 1907; Audit: correspondence of Allen Knight re minutes needed for the audit, Feb. 19, 1907 - Dec. 2, 1909; H. E. Huntington, correspondence re sale of Chevy Chase Land Company stocks, Feb. - Mar. 1907, 1907 Feb 25 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Charging of fees, a bill before the Cal. legislature - correspondence of Crothers, Jordan, A. T. Murray, Senator Marshall Black, Gov. J. N. Gillett, 1907 Mar 29 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Faculty housing (tract between Lasuen St. and Lagunita) - petition, correspondence; California Gas & Electric - right of way on Univ. land in Butte County, 1907 Mar 29 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Gamma Phi Beta Sorority building lot; Deed to W. C. Walker to lots in Alameda; Appraisal of Mrs. Stanford's jewels by Shreve and Co., 1907 Mar 29 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Report of organization committee and of Trustee Sloss on financial management; Proposed revised by-laws of the Board of Trustees and letter by Lathrop, 1907 Mar 29 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Salary and tenure; California Gas & Electric - right of way on Univ. land in Butte County; Lease of site of Stanford San Francisco home (stable site); Pacific Improvement Co. purchase of Champerico Road in Guatemala; Arboretum pedestrian path - petition to preserve; Sale of University lands (Berry Ranch), 1907 Apr 26 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Sixteenth Annual Commencement - program with notations; List of candiunitdates for degrees, with correspondence of J. M. Stillman and Crothers, 1907 May 22 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Northern Electric Company purchase of land in Butte Co. - Deeds, maps, correspondence; Vina Ranch - telegrams re agency for products in New York (Mr. Crovat deceased, Mrs. Crovat wishes to continue); Capital Traction Co. - stock matters; Summons and complaint from property suit of William T. Andrews and W. H. Mayn v. City of San Francisco, 1907 May 31 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Peninsular Railroad Company - Agreement with Trustees and supporting documents, letters, etc.; Investments - reports from Lathrop, Crothers on purchase of bonds, 1907 Jun 28 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Commission of Engineers of S. U. - report on reconstruction (mention of strike trouble) with list of comparative bids (4 pages), 1907 Aug 1 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Bridge over San Francisquito Creek - petition with map from Menlo Park residents and Trustees' denial; Board of Trustees, Lease for offices in Union Trust building; Notice of Completion of Work on Theta Delta Chi house [photocopy], 1907 Aug 30 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Proposed resolution on leaves of absence for University Professors; Printed copies of general resolution, 1903-1907, with related correspondence; Proposal for repair of Lagunita flume in connection with Student's Labor Day, with blueprint; Letter from Dr. Jordan stating the necessity and desirability of having the faculty live on campus; Receipt for some of Mrs. Stanford's personal jewelry to be placed in Stanford Museum - from Crothers; Earthquake damage report on Museum blueprint; Report to Chas. G. Lathrop from W. F. Durand (M. E. Dept.) on proposed installation of new rock crusher; Power House location and operation - special report by Durand; Sale of land in Butte Co. to Central Pacific Railway Co., 1907 Oct 4 (Box 2, Folder 11)